(678) 482-2158

[

Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services

(678) 482-2158](https://specialneedspt.com/)Toggle navigation

Privacy policy
--------------

#### (Revised September 2023)

* * *

**Scope**  
This statement applies to information collected while visiting this website.

**Personal Information**  
We collect information you choose to submit during your registration.  
We use common internet technologies, such as cookies and beacons, on our websites and emails.

**Uses**  
We use the information you submit to provide you with services you request.  
We use information about you to provide offers and information regarding services. We do not share, trade, or sell information about you with other marketers without providing you notice or obtaining your consent. We may share your information with affiliates, as well as vendors we have hired to assist in providing products and services.

**Important Information**  
Special Needs PT participates in the Safe Harbor program and adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the EU or Switzerland. For more information about the Safe Harbor program, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor website: http://export.gov/safeharbor/.

**How to Contact Us**:  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services  
Attn: Director, Privacy/Legal Dept.  
4411 Suwanee Dam Rd., Suite 435  
Suwanee, GA 30024  
Email: privacy@specialneedspt.com

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
At Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our pledge is to safeguard any personal information that you provide us, and to make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you choose. We are taking a leadership role in assisting our customers and other businesses in understanding the importance of using your personal information appropriately.

**Scope of this Notice**  
The goal of this Privacy Notice is to advise you of the online privacy practices relating using our website and domain. Customers from outside the U.S. may be presented with a policy applicable to their country of residence. For information about privacy policies regarding other types of data collection (such as offline collection) please use the contact information provided below.

**Collecting Your Personal Information**  
This Online Privacy Notice covers the collection and use of personal information on the site. Personal Information is data that reasonably can be used to identify or describe an individual. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services collects personal information online when:

* you submit questions or comments to us
* you request information or materials
* you register products online
* you request information be sent to you or your colleagues.  
    The type of information collected may include name, address, phone number, business contact information, billing and delivery information, email address, and other demographic information.

**Using Your Information**  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services uses the personal information you provide to:

* register you in programs
* create and maintain accounts
* answer your email
* send information you request
* send information to colleagues on your behalf  
    We also use this personal information to provide you with information related to your account, the products or services you purchased from us, to better understand your needs and interests, to improve our service, and to personalize communications.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services will not sell, rent, or trade the personal information you provide online without providing notice or obtaining your consent. However, Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services reserves the right to transfer your personal information in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets. We do share your personal information with certain Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services business affiliates. For a description of these business affiliates, please refer to the information located at the bottom of this page. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services may also disclose personal information to third parties without your consent for any of the following reasons: to comply with law, regulation or court order, to cooperate with Government investigations, to help prevent fraud, or to enforce or protect the rights of Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services or its subsidiaries.

**Your Choices about Receiving Email**  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services may send you email about your orders or your account and in response to your questions. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services may also send you email with information and/or special offers about products and services that may be of interest to you.  
Under most circumstances, we will give you an opportunity to let us know your preference regarding the receiving of promotional emails. This option applies to promotional emails only, as we may find it necessary to send you emails relating to your account, order, product, or pricing changes.

**Information Collected through Use of Cookies and Other Technologies**  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services automatically receives and records data on our servers from visitor browsers including computer IP (Internet Protocol) addresses and other information through the use of cookies. This information is collected about thousands of site visits and analyzed as a whole. This analysis looks for trends among many visitors to Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services or other Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services sites, and determines which parts of the site are accessed most frequently and what information visitors find most valuable.  
We may also collect and record information about what you viewed on our website. We may use this type of information and combine it with your personal information to help customize our future interactions with you. In doing so, we hope to provide better service to you by tailoring our communications to match your interests to give you more of what you want and less of what you don’t want.

**Protecting Your Information**  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services implements a variety of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures to help protect your personal information. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services has Internal Control Standards that relate specifically to the handling of personal information. These include certain controls to help safeguard the information we collect online. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services employees are trained to understand and comply with these controls and we communicate our privacy policy, practices, and guidelines to our employees.  
However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet.

**Communities**  
Some of our sites may enable you to participate in public services such as discussion boards, chats, and live events. Please use discretion when posting personal information about yourself when using these services. Be aware that when you disclose personal information at these sites, such as your name, member name, email address, etc., the information may be collected and used by others to send unsolicited emails. The services are open to the public, and what you post there can be seen by anyone and is not protected. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services cannot control the comments that you may receive while you participate in these services. You may find other people’s comments to be offensive, harmful, or inaccurate.

**Outside Links**  
Some Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services web pages contain links to and from other websites and Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services is not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services encourages you to ascertain the privacy practices of those websites.

**Keeping Your Information Accurate**  
If you are a registered user, you can review and update your profile using your user name and password. You can also contact your Customer Service representative.

**How to Reach Us**  
If you have questions or concerns about your privacy when using the Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services website, please contact us by mail at:  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services  
Attn: Director, Privacy/Legal Dept.  
4411 Suwanee Dam Rd., Suite 435  
Suwanee, GA 30024  
Email: privacy@specialneedspt.com  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services will work with you to resolve any concerns you have about this policy.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice**  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services reserves the right to modify this privacy notice from time to time, by posting a prominent announcement on this page or, in the event of a material change, by notifying by email all customers whose personal information we have retained.

**Who are Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services’s “business affiliates”?**  
Companies who assist Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services to complete or follow-up on your order  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services may share your personal information, as necessary, with companies who contract with Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services to fulfill and/or ship an order, an award, or rebate; conduct surveys; assist in the processing of our accounts and managing our systems; collect payments; facilitate email subscriptions; or provide a product or service you have requested. We require these companies to use the shared information only for these limited purposes.  
Other Commercial Partners  
Personal information received from our commercial customers may be provided to other commercial partners (such as dealers and distributors) to provide you products, services, or other information about products and services that may be of interest to your business.

**What are “cookies” and how does Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services use them?**  
Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive, at a website’s request. Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services cookies do not contain any personal information and are used for these reasons:

1. cookies allow us to keep track of the pictures you upload and download;
2. cookies allow us to remember you when you login to the places on our site which require Membership;
3. to remember your country and language preferences;
4. to help us understand the size of our audience and traffic patterns; to manage and present site information;
5. to deliver information specific to your interests; and
6. to manage site information and pictures displayed on your computer.

**Do I have to have a cookie set to use this site?**  
Special Needs Pediatric Therapy Services can be accessed with cookies disabled; however, your visit will be significantly enhanced if cookies are enabled. Some parts of the site will require cookies to be enabled.  
You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Please click on the “Help” menu of your browser for information on setting cookie preferences.

Helpful links
